oh yeah you do a little refill my moves
Chicago I started like oh I went to a
place the the old the Green Mill and you
could sit now Capone's booth where you
could see both actresses in the
bartender my friend ran a place to be
like oh look behind the bar
here's tunnels there's tunnels were
alkapone used to go and it's not so much
that he just was ruthlessly killed
people but he was dumb hello today we're
gonna talk about Alphonse Capone a hot
doggy lipped gangster Al Capone went to
Chicago we got more guns and more guys
more money and faster cars it was just
like boom I guess we'll just take over
the city it was like really that simple
prohibition delivered this country to Al
Capone bound and gagged just the liquor
was so lucrative
you know and the money just kept piling
up and was like became like literally a
kabillion in it guy was like 90 IQ
pretty weird he was the most powerful
man everyone knew it press conference
was to say like why don't you made mayor
Al and he'd like laughs they'll just be
in this position why would I be bear you
know so many rules ton of Bulls I was
like they were looking for a way to take
him down and he never claimed that he
had any income Herbert Hoover stepped in
and just said like okay we're finding
him guilty and here's the story
George nerd is in on it his brother was
busted for tax evasion we could get Al
Capone on tax evasion Eliot Ness was
Treasury Treasury agent said like George
you're gonna can testify he didn't want
to do it because he was like yeah you
the Al Capone's more powerful than the
government this comes down from upstairs
look Mookie it was like really that
simple you know so you know you got this
like hot doggy lift 90 IQ getting weird
I was just like how about we go to them
and say all right let's say I made this
much money over this period of time and
I'll pay this kind of taxes
and I'll plea bargain and had it
negotiated where he was gonna do two
years in prison and then the judge said
like we're not gonna accept your plea
but we're gonna take part of your plea
that said you earned this much money and
bust you for taxes and and sentence you
to 11 years in prison so I was like well
what the thought we had a deal here they
put him away that's when they started
giving him like you know a medical tests
and psych tests and stuff and that's you
know cuz really they knew nothing about
him he's got a 95 IQ he's not that smart
he's this big weird
Moke I got a 90 IQ but you sure knew who
to kill and that's pretty smart oh and
he started peeing pus when he was 18
years old they didn't wouldn't say
anything about it
syphilis syphilis he just ignored
husking coming out of his I mean right
god fusses coming out of my what is it
nothing what are you gonna do I'm gonna
stop thinking about it good idea
hey how about one penicillin shot nope
let's ignore it and you know it's afraid
of needles and syphilis rots his brain
soon after he becomes in battling idiot
do you know he is he wanted his nickname
to be snorky I want to be called snorky
we're gonna call you Scarface I want to
be called snorky
but when he got out of jail he really
quickly wandered away into like a idiot
who would like put a fishing pole in it
was like pool in his backyard like
hoping to catch fish imagine they just
made comments like hey why is he fishing
in his own pool he's athletic it's
athletic more I'm what saying it's a guy
who's as portion it was brain eaten away
by his own pus he's he's he's he's a
he's like a five-year-old Wow
because he had sex with and he
got like a dirty dick and he didn't do
anything about it
pretty much the most powerful man in you
know the country like looking for fake
fish in a pool with a his bamboo rod
well it wasn't idiot he had everything
right
you